import React from 'react'

let science = {
    title: "Science",
    questions: [
        {   
            question: "Of the following, this is not a noble gas",
            answers: ["Boron", "Neon", "Radon", "Helium"],
            correct: "Boron"
        },
        {   
            question: "The thickest skin on the human body is found here",
            answers: ["Bum", "Palm", "Back", "Head"],
            correct: "Palm"
        },
        {   
            question: "Joseph Bombardier invented this in 1936",
            answers: ["Electric Car", "Solar Battery", "Motorcycle", "Snowmobile"],
            correct: "Snowmobile"
        },
        {   
            question: "This man helped create penicillin",
            answers: ["Fleming", "Roux", "Salk", "Crick"],
            correct: "Fleming"
        },
        {   
            question: "This scientist won the Nobel Prize for his work in quantum theory and atomic structure",
            answers: ["Bohr", "Olivier", "Page", "Abt"],
            correct: "Bohr"
        },
        {   
            question: "This man developed the Google search engine along with Larry Page",
            answers: ["Clark", "Jones", "Javan", "Brin"],
            correct: "Brin"
        },
        {   
            question: "Cytology is the study of this",
            answers: ["Cells", "Magnets", "Large Cats", "Maps"],
            correct: "Cells"
        },
        {   
            question: "Bamboo is known for this",
            answers: ["The fastest growing plant", "Having 2 colors of flowers", "Having above ground roots", "Grow at night"],
            correct: "The fastest growing plant"
        },
        {   
            question: "This culture invented the abacus",
            answers: ["Chinese", "Russian", "Egyptian", "Mayan"],
            correct: "Chinese"
        },
        {   
            question: "This is the other name for vitamin A",
            answers: ["Riboflavin", "Thiamin", "Retinol", "Niacin"],
            correct: "Retinol"
        },
        {   
            question: "The Electric battery was invented in this year",
            answers: ["1876", "1967", "1800", "1903"],
            correct: "1800"
        },
        {   
            question: "Venus and this planet are sometimes called the Blue Planet",
            answers: ["Neptune", "Mars", "Mercury", "Earth"],
            correct: "Earth"
        },
        {   
            question: "The hypodermic syringe was invented during this war",
            answers: ["WWI", "100 year war", "WWII", "Civil War"],
            correct: "Civil War"
        },
        {   
            question: "This invention dates back to 1500 BC",
            answers: ["Paintbrush", "Comb", "Glass", "Paper"],
            correct: "Glass"
        },
        {   
            question: "Mariner 9 orbited this planet in 1971",
            answers: ["Mercury", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
            correct: "Mars"
        },
        {   
            question: "This organ fights infections and filters foreign objects",
            answers: ["Pancreas", "Kidney", "Spleen", "Liver"],
            correct: "Spleen"
        },
        {   
            question: "Agent Orange is this",
            answers: ["Cartoon character", "Math problem", "Element Nickname", "Herbicide"],
            correct: "Herbicide"
        },
        {   
            question: "This scientist has not won a Nobel Prize for chemistry",
            answers: ["Erti", "Fischer", "Higgs", "Currie"],
            correct: "Higgs"
        },
        {   
            question: "This item was not invented in 1965",
            answers: ["Optical Disk", "Hypertext", "Respirator", "Cash dispenser"],
            correct: "Cash dispenser"
        },
        {   
            question: "This percentage of the population has an IQ above 100",
            answers: ["50", "80", "70", "60"],
            correct: "50"
        }
    ]
}

export default science